

Marcos Campos

- 🛮 Brasília, DF 📞 61998750918 🚇 marcos.b.campos14@gmail.com
- https://github.com/marcos-c1

Resumo

I'm a Computer Science student at Federal Institute of Brasília to get the bachelor's degree in the current course. I have professional experience acquired through academic and freelance competitions, as well as knowledge through improvements made throughout the academic journey. My notable qualities include proactivity, resilience and dedication, characteristics that make me stand out in the technology field.

Experience

Public Ministry of the Federal District and Territories, 09/2017 - 12/2017 Asa Sul

Estagiário

Asa Sul, Brasília

I worked in the Due Diligence department, my purpose was to update the procedural data in the system. Furthermore, he performed functions related to archiving cases and forwarding them to the appropriate courts.

Brazilian Hospital Services Company (EBSERH)

11/2020 - 04/2022

Estagiário

Asa Sul. DF

https://www.gov.br/ebserh/pt-br

I worked on the Personnel Analysis and Dimensioning Sector in the Data Science area, with the objective of providing efficient analytical tools based on the manipulation of data from the data warehouse.

Federal Audit Court (TCU)

03/2022 - 03/2024

Estagiário

Asa Sul. DF

https://portal.tcu.gov.br/inicio/

I worked as a backend developer on TCU's Radex integrative system using pure JavaScript. The agile methodology applied is SCRUM; The main objective of the application is to provide users with an interactive interface around the deliberations of each process carried out by the control body's committees.

Caronas Burguer

11/2023 - 01/2024

Freelancer

Tag. Norte, DF

https://www.caronasburger.com.br/

I worked as a frontend developer with the aim of making the application responsive, consistent and interactive with the user. The entire application is developed in pure PHP and the server is hosted by Apache.

Educação

Taguatinga Educational Center 05

02/2015 - 12/2017 High School

Federal Institute of Brasília, Taguatinga Campus

02/2019 - Studying University education

https://www.ifb.edu.br/taguatinga

Skills

JavaScript, HTML, CSS

••••

CRUD em APIs Restful Protocolo HTTPS, SOAP

••••

Ferramenta low-code

Oracle APEX, Power BI, Power Query

••••

Banco de Dados

MySQL, SQL Server, MongoDB, PostGreSQL, PL/SQL

••••

Deploy da aplicação em Nuvem Microsoft Azure, Amazon AWS

• • • • •

Frameworks Front-End

ReactJS, VueJS, NextJS, Redux, GraphQL

••••

Frameworks Back-End

Express, Angular, JQuery

••••

Languages

C/C++, Java, Python, Perl/Bash, JavaScript, VBA, PL/SQL

• • • • 0